[
  {
    "idx": "1",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-3.97, 8.97, -5.87) around the axis (-0.36, 0.78, -0.52) by an angle 4.23 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-4.28, 8.99, -5.9]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "2",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (3.35, 2.55, 1.42), (4.88, -1.47, 2.44) and (2.56, -4.26, -2.83), (-0.33, 8.88, 5.64).",
    "answer": "[[3.07, 3.28, 1.23]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "3",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-4.85, 8.57, 6.36):\n[[ 0.06  0.48  0.76 -7.74]\n [ 0.3  -0.86 -0.89  6.65]\n [ 0.41 -0.46  0.72  1.06]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[0.92, -7.84, -0.29]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "4",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-0.45, -4.25, 2.0) to the plane with the equation -3.08x + 2.79y + 1.45z + 1.68 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[1.34]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "5",
    "question": "Project the point (-9.65, -3.34, 1.83) onto the line passing through points (-3.1, 9.23, 8.33) and (6.86, 9.56, -4.09).",
    "answer": "[[-2.65, 9.24, 7.77]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "6",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-9.58, -1.44) around the center point (-1.54, -5.72) by an angle 2.5 radians.",
    "answer": "[[2.34, -13.96]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "7",
    "question": "Project the point (-3.81, -5.56, 0.77) onto the plane with the equation 7.75x + 6.66y + -0.32z + 5.5 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[0.74, -1.65, 0.58]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "8",
    "question": "Rotate the point (4.51, 1.31, -4.43) around the axis (-0.54, -0.55, 0.63) by an angle 2.83 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[2.47, 5.27, -2.55]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "9",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-5.15-2.43j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[5.69, -2.7]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "10",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 3.68, Angle: 2.57) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-3.1, 1.99]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "11",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 788 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1100010100, 1424, 314]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "12",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1111001111 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[975, 1717, 3cf]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "13",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 38 in 15-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[111111111011001]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "14",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 4.09, Theta: 2.49, Phi: 6.25) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[2.48, -0.08, -3.25]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "15",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -2.75, Y: -1.67, Z: 4.79) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[5.77, 0.59, -2.6]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "16",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 8.73 and phase 5.35 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[5.2, -7.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "17",
    "question": "Rotate the point (7.87, -0.35) by an angle 3.03 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-7.78, 1.22]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "18",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 22.37 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 71.24 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 26.22 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.02, 2237.0, 0.0, 26220.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "19",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-9.43, 7.48, -7.99) around the axis (0.96, 0.28, 0.05) by an angle 3.97 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-3.54, -13.81, -2.45]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "20",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (0.99, 6.76, 2.66), (3.23, -7.6, 1.96) and (-6.55, -7.5, 8.52), (-3.11, 7.86, 7.22).",
    "answer": "[[-1.19, 20.76, 3.34]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "21",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-0.3, 6.93, -3.21):\n[[ 0.97 -0.41 -0.2   7.2 ]\n [-0.94  0.44 -0.84  1.86]\n [ 0.16  0.58  0.07  1.99]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[4.71, 7.89, 5.74]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "22",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-6.67, -8.93, -8.85) to the plane with the equation -5.78x + 8.7y + -3.02z + 2.88 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[0.88]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "23",
    "question": "Project the point (5.81, -2.88, 1.01) onto the line passing through points (1.73, -9.99, -9.37) and (-7.55, 1.37, 5.53).",
    "answer": "[[-2.46, -4.86, -2.64]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "24",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-0.54, 7.12) around the center point (-0.44, -1.14) by an angle 4.32 radians.",
    "answer": "[[7.23, -4.21]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "25",
    "question": "Project the point (5.49, 6.28, -8.94) onto the plane with the equation -7.81x + -5.82y + -4.8z + -8.36 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[2.52, 4.06, -10.77]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "26",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-6.61, 7.6, -9.8) around the axis (-0.7, 0.32, 0.64) by an angle 1.35 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-9.68, -8.96, -4.88]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "27",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (0.8+4.12j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[4.2, 1.38]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "28",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 2.56, Angle: 4.78) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[0.17, -2.55]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "29",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 578 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1001000010, 1102, 242]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "30",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1001001010 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[586, 1112, 24a]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "31",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 86 in 8-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[10101001]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "32",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 1.86, Theta: 2.16, Phi: 1.8) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-0.35, 1.51, -1.03]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "33",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 0.65, Y: -5.96, Z: -1.73) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[6.24, 1.85, -1.46]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "34",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 1.33 and phase 3.15 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-1.33, -0.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "35",
    "question": "Rotate the point (4.5, -3.23) by an angle 0.73 radians.",
    "answer": "[[5.51, 0.59]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "36",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 54.5 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 16.98 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 70.35 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.05, 5450.0, 0.0, 70350.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "37",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.85, 2.11, 8.61) around the axis (-0.97, 0.16, 0.18) by an angle 2.81 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[4.6, -0.84, -11.61]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "38",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (9.94, 2.21, 7.52), (4.69, 8.6, 0.48) and (9.99, -2.4, -8.38), (4.38, -7.01, -9.27).",
    "answer": "[[6.44, 6.47, 2.83]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "39",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-4.67, 1.68, 2.43):\n[[ 0.49 -0.99 -0.72  6.81]\n [-0.94 -0.98 -0.36  9.01]\n [-0.24 -0.12  0.47  2.29]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[1.11, 10.88, 4.35]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "40",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-0.7, 9.42, -1.65) to the plane with the equation -2.54x + -6.07y + 9.79z + 0.0 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[6.07]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "41",
    "question": "Project the point (5.39, -1.11, 0.75) onto the line passing through points (-0.25, 3.33, 0.73) and (2.31, -9.6, 7.03).",
    "answer": "[[0.61, -1.03, 2.85]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "42",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-9.12, -5.55) around the center point (6.31, 9.41) by an angle 3.08 radians.",
    "answer": "[[22.63, 23.39]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "43",
    "question": "Project the point (-2.94, -1.84, 9.6) onto the plane with the equation -0.64x + 6.58y + -7.72z + 9.57 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-3.4, 2.92, 4.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "44",
    "question": "Rotate the point (4.64, 5.92, -5.68) around the axis (-0.59, 0.64, 0.49) by an angle 0.69 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-0.35, 3.63, -8.69]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "45",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-4.56+8.19j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[9.37, 2.08]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "46",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 6.96, Angle: 1.5) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[0.49, 6.94]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "47",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 203 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[11001011, 313, cb]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "48",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1100100001 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[801, 1441, 321]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "49",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -43 in 10-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[0000101010]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "50",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 5.15, Theta: 2.97, Phi: 1.84) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-0.23, 0.85, -5.07]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "51",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -4.03, Y: -2.91, Z: 1.71) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[5.26, 1.24, -2.52]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "52",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 5.68 and phase 1.35 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.24, 5.54]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "53",
    "question": "Rotate the point (9.39, 9.62) by an angle 5.57 radians.",
    "answer": "[[13.4, 1.13]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "54",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 71.84 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 80.77 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 12.18 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.07, 7184.0, 0.0, 12180.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "55",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-6.27, 2.41, 7.61) around the axis (-0.63, -0.64, 0.44) by an angle 6.05 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-4.83, 1.77, 8.75]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "56",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-3.07, 5.05, 3.82), (-0.72, 8.17, 8.19) and (6.19, 5.02, 6.48), (-2.13, -7.19, 9.75).",
    "answer": "[[-1.23, 7.49, 7.23]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "57",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (6.5, 2.72, -1.42):\n[[-0.48  0.96  0.63  3.05]\n [-0.45  0.22  0.71 -5.39]\n [ 0.68 -0.28  0.55 -4.17]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[1.65, -8.72, -1.29]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "58",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-3.04, -0.02, 3.75) to the plane with the equation 0.61x + 0.47y + 4.21z + -9.18 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[1.11]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "59",
    "question": "Project the point (-5.29, -2.63, 7.44) onto the line passing through points (-4.38, 2.56, 1.39) and (7.87, -3.23, 1.92).",
    "answer": "[[-2.91, 1.86, 1.45]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "60",
    "question": "Rotate the point (6.7, -7.01) around the center point (-0.67, 6.44) by an angle 3.29 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-9.95, 18.65]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "61",
    "question": "Project the point (6.73, -0.76, 8.38) onto the plane with the equation 6.33x + -1.44y + 3.47z + -8.91 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-0.73, 0.94, 4.29]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "62",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-9.51, 2.69, -9.79) around the axis (-0.66, 0.54, 0.52) by an angle 2.59 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[1.37, -5.63, 12.64]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "63",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-4.04+4.54j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[6.08, 2.3]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "64",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 1.58, Angle: 4.53) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-0.29, -1.55]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "65",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 271 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[100001111, 417, 10f]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "66",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1100001011 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[779, 1413, 3]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "67",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 82 in 13-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[1111110101101]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "68",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 9.85, Theta: 2.3, Phi: 2.71) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-6.67, 3.07, -6.56]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "69",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 8.59, Y: -2.25, Z: -6.41) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[10.95, 2.2, -0.26]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "70",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 7.95 and phase 4.89 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.4, -7.82]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "71",
    "question": "Rotate the point (9.49, -7.3) by an angle 3.22 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-10.03, 6.53]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "72",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 6.9 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 92.21 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 63.77 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.01, 690.0, 0.0, 63770.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "73",
    "question": "Rotate the point (0.38, -1.69, -8.97) around the axis (-0.86, 0.26, -0.45) by an angle 6.1 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[0.89, -0.21, -9.09]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "74",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-4.76, -3.94, 7.93), (-9.67, -0.38, 1.75) and (6.1, 2.52, 7.06), (7.67, 8.72, -5.54).",
    "answer": "[[3.79, -10.14, 18.7]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "75",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (9.12, 8.33, -2.99):\n[[-0.41 -0.97 -0.59 -2.65]\n [ 0.42 -0.47  0.44 -5.8 ]\n [ 0.98 -0.19  0.56  6.94]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-12.71, -7.2, 12.62]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "76",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (4.71, 0.47, 7.36) to the plane with the equation -5.75x + -8.26y + -1.44z + 1.81 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[3.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "77",
    "question": "Project the point (6.11, -5.92, -2.5) onto the line passing through points (4.6, 8.29, -7.11) and (-6.1, 6.18, 3.05).",
    "answer": "[[1.68, 7.71, -4.34]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "78",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-3.02, -4.59) around the center point (-3.69, 0.23) by an angle 3.83 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-7.27, 3.53]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "79",
    "question": "Project the point (5.19, -0.86, -9.87) onto the plane with the equation 0.06x + -0.36y + 3.44z + -5.52 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[5.38, -2.03, 1.3]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "80",
    "question": "Rotate the point (3.65, -5.11, -5.45) around the axis (0.4, 0.24, 0.89) by an angle 6.03 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[2.66, -6.34, -4.68]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "81",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (6.82-3.22j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[7.54, -0.44]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "82",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 9.83, Angle: 4.51) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-1.98, -9.63]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "83",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 396 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[110001100, 614, 18c]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "84",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 110010000 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[400, 620, 190]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "85",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -22 in 13-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[0000000010101]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "86",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 1.88, Theta: 0.3, Phi: 3.89) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-0.41, -0.38, 1.8]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "87",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 4.38, Y: 3.06, Z: 1.74) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[5.62, 1.26, 0.61]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "88",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 6.93 and phase 0.55 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[5.91, 3.62]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "89",
    "question": "Rotate the point (1.44, 6.49) by an angle 1.04 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-4.87, 4.53]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "90",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 91.95 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 27.32 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 10.63 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.09, 9195.0, 0.0, 10630.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "91",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-4.58, -5.8, 9.37) around the axis (-0.33, -0.83, 0.45) by an angle 3.0 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-3.12, -11.52, -0.1]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "92",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (5.75, 5.38, 8.73), (-3.34, 8.71, -2.24) and (8.05, 8.75, 0.27), (8.86, -0.12, -5.84).",
    "answer": "[[2.36, 6.62, 4.63]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "93",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (0.97, 5.83, 9.01):\n[[ 0.26 -0.34 -0.39  4.61]\n [-0.59 -0.34  0.46  8.42]\n [ 0.04 -0.59 -0.23 -7.57]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-0.63, 10.01, -13.04]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "94",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-3.35, -7.75, 0.84) to the plane with the equation 2.05x + -5.6y + 2.86z + -8.0 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[4.68]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "95",
    "question": "Project the point (7.03, -1.04, -7.49) onto the line passing through points (1.15, -5.46, -1.48) and (-1.61, 0.14, 1.92).",
    "answer": "[[1.8, -6.78, -2.28]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "96",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.68, -9.58) around the center point (3.0, -5.33) by an angle 4.62 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-1.76, -10.59]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "97",
    "question": "Project the point (-9.13, -4.96, 3.01) onto the plane with the equation 3.4x + 4.71y + -2.82z + 8.65 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-4.71, 1.17, -0.66]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "98",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-2.47, -0.97, -1.4) around the axis (-0.57, 0.55, 0.61) by an angle 4.72 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[0.15, 2.31, -1.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "99",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-6.12-6.21j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[8.72, -2.35]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "100",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 1.91, Angle: 1.16) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[0.76, 1.75]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "101",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 699 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1010111011, 1273, 2bb]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "102",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1000110001 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[561, 1061, 231]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "103",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 90 in 15-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[111111110100101]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "104",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 6.05, Theta: 2.79, Phi: 5.58) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[1.59, -1.35, -5.68]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "105",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -5.63, Y: -0.11, Z: 9.95) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[11.43, 0.51, -3.12]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "106",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 2.71 and phase 1.74 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-0.46, 2.67]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "107",
    "question": "Rotate the point (1.77, -1.1) by an angle 2.3 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-0.36, 2.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "108",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 40.98 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 14.62 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 76.37 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.04, 4098.0, 0.0, 76370.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "109",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-7.29, 5.95, 8.48) around the axis (-0.61, -0.28, 0.74) by an angle 0.32 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-9.33, 5.45, 6.61]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "110",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-5.22, -9.66, -6.88), (-6.2, -7.98, -9.53) and (5.88, 0.39, 7.56), (-2.08, -7.44, -6.15).",
    "answer": "[[-5.72, -8.81, -8.22]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "111",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (8.32, 5.67, 2.07):\n[[ 0.17  0.45  0.13 -3.01]\n [-0.62  0.46  0.46  2.05]\n [ 0.9  -0.78 -0.82 -0.02]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[1.23, 0.45, 1.35]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "112",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (0.42, 6.6, 6.67) to the plane with the equation -3.02x + 4.68y + -2.85z + -2.12 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[1.36]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "113",
    "question": "Project the point (-3.26, -5.84, -8.2) onto the line passing through points (1.79, -3.51, 1.14) and (-1.91, 3.4, -8.92).",
    "answer": "[[-0.41, 0.59, -4.83]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "114",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-7.67, 8.58) around the center point (9.74, 8.48) by an angle 3.47 radians.",
    "answer": "[[26.25, 14.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "115",
    "question": "Project the point (-1.82, 8.7, 3.78) onto the plane with the equation -8.82x + -4.57y + 7.23z + -3.69 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-1.82, 8.7, 3.78]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "116",
    "question": "Rotate the point (3.41, -7.43, -2.6) around the axis (-0.5, -0.11, 0.86) by an angle 4.01 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-4.73, 4.12, -5.86]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "117",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (3.43-2.4j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[4.19, -0.61]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "118",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 6.65, Angle: 1.47) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[0.67, 6.62]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "119",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 145 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[10010001, 221, 91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "120",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1111000111 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[967, 1707, 3c7]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "121",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 90 in 14-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[11111110100101]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "122",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 9.08, Theta: 0.07, Phi: 0.81) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[0.44, 0.46, 9.06]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "123",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 9.89, Y: -6.67, Z: -5.22) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[13.02, 1.98, -0.59]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "124",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 5.75 and phase 1.39 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.03, 5.66]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "125",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-7.34, 8.81) by an angle 6.08 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-5.41, 10.11]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "126",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 16.78 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 74.9 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 14.59 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.02, 1678.0, 0.0, 14590.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "127",
    "question": "Rotate the point (9.83, -1.46, 0.51) around the axis (0.31, -0.94, 0.14) by an angle 2.01 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-2.44, -4.29, 8.63]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "128",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (1.96, -9.11, -4.32), (2.06, 7.43, 1.94) and (4.45, 0.46, 0.95), (-9.95, -8.61, 7.77).",
    "answer": "[[2.02, 0.63, -0.63]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "129",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (5.72, 5.65, 9.43):\n[[-0.59 -0.03  0.63 -1.31]\n [ 0.67  0.54  0.83  1.4 ]\n [ 0.16  0.13  0.78 -7.64]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[1.09, 16.11, 1.37]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "130",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-4.84, -7.8, -9.59) to the plane with the equation 2.18x + 4.64y + 4.66z + 6.37 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[12.28]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "131",
    "question": "Project the point (3.26, -7.01, -0.91) onto the line passing through points (-3.99, 9.43, 1.74) and (-5.01, 8.47, 8.79).",
    "answer": "[[-3.79, 9.62, 0.34]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "132",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-7.9, 6.72) around the center point (-8.68, 9.27) by an angle 2.12 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-6.91, 11.27]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "133",
    "question": "Project the point (2.5, -8.95, 6.21) onto the plane with the equation -6.89x + 7.4y + 8.93z + 0.24 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[1.45, -7.82, 7.57]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "134",
    "question": "Rotate the point (3.1, -4.39, 3.84) around the axis (-0.37, -0.91, 0.16) by an angle 4.49 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[0.48, -4.75, -4.51]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "135",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (7.46+7.1j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[10.3, 0.76]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "136",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 4.82, Angle: 5.47) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[3.31, -3.5]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "137",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 611 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1001100011, 1143, 263]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "138",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1100111010 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[826, 1472, 33a]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "139",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -50 in 15-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[000000000110001]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "140",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 6.78, Theta: 2.71, Phi: 4.67) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-0.12, -2.83, -6.16]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "141",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 6.68, Y: 0.57, Z: -5.0) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[8.36, 2.21, 0.09]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "142",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 8.12 and phase 1.33 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.94, 7.89]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "143",
    "question": "Rotate the point (0.09, -3.01) by an angle 3.24 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-0.39, 2.99]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "144",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 91.61 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 5.71 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 72.39 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.09, 9161.0, 0.0, 72390.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "145",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-1.89, -7.27, -5.42) around the axis (-0.24, -0.4, -0.88) by an angle 2.14 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-5.55, -0.78, -7.26]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "146",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-4.13, 3.49, -3.19), (-7.84, 6.19, 1.1) and (2.52, 7.63, 0.19), (7.7, 5.49, -1.56).",
    "answer": "[[-12.36, 9.48, 6.33]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "147",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (5.03, 2.35, -3.44):\n[[-0.69  0.01  0.18  2.2 ]\n [-0.78 -0.59 -0.93 -2.86]\n [ 0.26  0.75 -0.43  9.78]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-1.87, -4.97, 14.33]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "148",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (0.49, 2.52, -2.27) to the plane with the equation -9.74x + -8.88y + -7.53z + -6.55 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[1.09]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "149",
    "question": "Project the point (-2.63, -6.45, -7.97) onto the line passing through points (9.26, 9.66, -1.4) and (2.45, 3.72, 2.12).",
    "answer": "[[-1.86, -0.04, 4.35]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "150",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-2.71, 7.68) around the center point (-7.92, 3.1) by an angle 5.98 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-1.58, 5.92]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "151",
    "question": "Project the point (-6.26, 5.13, -5.63) onto the plane with the equation -5.51x + -2.13y + -9.29z + -1.7 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-2.89, 6.43, 0.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "152",
    "question": "Rotate the point (9.82, -6.32, 9.82) around the axis (0.66, 0.62, -0.41) by an angle 5.96 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[8.15, -2.7, 12.6]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "153",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-1.13+7.95j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[8.03, 1.71]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "154",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 8.27, Angle: 4.2) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-4.05, -7.21]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "155",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 381 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[101111101, 575, 17d]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "156",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 100100011 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[291, 443, 123]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "157",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -44 in 14-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[00000000101011]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "158",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 7.16, Theta: 0.93, Phi: 5.96) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[5.44, -1.82, 4.28]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "159",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -5.89, Y: -7.67, Z: 5.59) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[11.17, 1.05, -2.23]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "160",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 5.81 and phase 0.36 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[5.44, 2.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "161",
    "question": "Rotate the point (5.42, -2.01) by an angle 1.31 radians.",
    "answer": "[[3.34, 4.72]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "162",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 13.17 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 93.81 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 18.94 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.01, 1317.0, 0.0, 18940.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "163",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.65, -1.98, -7.81) around the axis (0.28, -0.49, 0.82) by an angle 1.55 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[4.8, 10.68, 1.1]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "164",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-0.76, -4.31, -6.47), (-2.16, 3.78, 4.14) and (-8.87, -7.64, 9.44), (8.46, 0.01, 2.82).",
    "answer": "[[-1.8, 1.68, 1.38]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "165",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (1.38, -5.76, 2.34):\n[[ 0.08  0.66 -0.73 -5.92]\n [ 0.24  0.05 -0.06 -6.3 ]\n [ 0.9  -0.96 -0.88  4.3 ]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-11.32, -6.4, 9.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "166",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-0.35, -1.36, 7.14) to the plane with the equation -8.91x + -3.55y + -5.12z + 5.6 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[2.12]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "167",
    "question": "Project the point (-7.55, 0.11, 5.21) onto the line passing through points (-5.06, 5.74, 5.99) and (-1.92, 2.99, 1.61).",
    "answer": "[[-4.11, 4.91, 4.66]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "168",
    "question": "Rotate the point (3.38, 8.08) around the center point (-6.06, -1.96) by an angle 5.33 radians.",
    "answer": "[[7.59, -3.84]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "169",
    "question": "Project the point (-1.1, 4.15, -1.91) onto the plane with the equation 5.97x + 3.98y + -1.23z + 4.77 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-3.02, 2.87, -1.51]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "170",
    "question": "Rotate the point (4.33, -6.32, -5.55) around the axis (-0.42, 0.85, 0.32) by an angle 1.7 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[1.02, -8.73, -3.54]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "171",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-1.68+3.52j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[3.9, 2.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "172",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 6.72, Angle: 2.47) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-5.26, 4.18]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "173",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 464 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[111010000, 720, 1d0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "174",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1000001010 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[522, 1012, 20a]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "175",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 51 in 12-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[111111001100]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "176",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 7.38, Theta: 0.32, Phi: 2.14) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-1.25, 1.96, 7.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "177",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -8.18, Y: -0.43, Z: -2.23) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[8.49, 1.84, -3.09]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "178",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 6.42 and phase 6.22 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[6.41, -0.41]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "179",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.2, -8.18) by an angle 0.53 radians.",
    "answer": "[[11.21, -2.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "180",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 88.67 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 65.11 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 61.13 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.09, 8867.0, 0.0, 61130.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "181",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.66, 6.16, -7.48) around the axis (-0.94, 0.34, 0.08) by an angle 3.97 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[6.85, -3.28, 10.6]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "182",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-2.83, 7.97, 7.23), (-6.88, 7.01, 8.98) and (5.51, 2.25, -6.39), (4.78, 7.29, -0.69).",
    "answer": "[[4.85, 9.79, 3.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "183",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (8.49, 2.05, 4.46):\n[[-0.7   0.69  0.07  8.17]\n [ 0.84  0.35  0.3   8.93]\n [-0.55  0.77  0.08  8.74]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[3.95, 18.12, 6.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "184",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (3.02, -2.14, -2.77) to the plane with the equation -4.61x + -8.64y + -7.49z + -6.7 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[1.51]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "185",
    "question": "Project the point (-3.71, 0.08, 8.66) onto the line passing through points (2.01, -3.61, -4.17) and (2.75, -5.52, 8.74).",
    "answer": "[[2.68, -5.34, 7.49]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "186",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-9.66, 0.29) around the center point (0.55, -5.24) by an angle 0.28 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-10.79, -2.75]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "187",
    "question": "Project the point (0.54, -6.9, 3.25) onto the plane with the equation -7.44x + -7.2y + 8.28z + -4.69 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[3.41, -4.12, 0.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "188",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.81, -9.35, -0.08) around the axis (0.73, -0.48, 0.48) by an angle 3.35 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[6.16, -2.07, 10.95]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "189",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (0.16-9.76j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[9.76, -1.55]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "190",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 6.91, Angle: 1.37) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.38, 6.77]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "191",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 624 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1001110000, 1160, 270]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "192",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1101100001 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[865, 1541, 361]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "193",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -94 in 9-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[001011101]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "194",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 6.9, Theta: 0.71, Phi: 4.29) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-1.84, -4.1, 5.23]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "195",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -6.51, Y: 0.83, Z: 8.15) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[10.46, 0.68, 3.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "196",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 8.34 and phase 5.83 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[7.5, -3.65]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "197",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-2.29, 3.56) by an angle 2.32 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-1.05, -4.1]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "198",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 45.0 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 4.13 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 78.66 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.04, 4500.0, 0.0, 78660.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "199",
    "question": "Rotate the point (9.43, 3.74, -2.29) around the axis (0.37, -0.93, -0.05) by an angle 6.22 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[9.26, 3.71, -2.93]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "200",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (4.38, 3.27, -9.89), (5.29, 2.34, 3.9) and (6.92, -7.43, 1.55), (-5.17, -3.35, -6.31).",
    "answer": "[[4.97, 2.67, -1.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "201",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-9.43, -2.05, -9.85):\n[[ 0.73 -0.38  0.55  0.1 ]\n [ 0.76  0.59 -0.46 -1.35]\n [-0.05  0.31  0.62  1.9 ]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-11.42, -5.2, -4.37]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "202",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (7.98, -8.81, 5.2) to the plane with the equation -3.58x + -9.84y + 1.34z + -6.79 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[5.52]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "203",
    "question": "Project the point (-2.27, 1.47, -1.36) onto the line passing through points (9.58, 5.51, 7.93) and (-6.47, 2.96, 8.99).",
    "answer": "[[-1.96, 3.68, 8.69]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "204",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-3.54, 2.57) around the center point (-9.99, -6.34) by an angle 2.97 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-17.87, -14.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "205",
    "question": "Project the point (8.0, 5.2, -1.44) onto the plane with the equation 0.03x + -6.74y + -1.76z + -2.67 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[8.02, 0.35, -2.71]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "206",
    "question": "Rotate the point (4.61, 9.03, 4.11) around the axis (-0.93, -0.02, -0.38) by an angle 3.67 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[4.78, -8.62, 4.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "207",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (5.04+3.13j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[5.93, 0.56]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "208",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 9.36, Angle: 1.59) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-0.18, 9.36]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "209",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 389 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[110000101, 605, 185]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "210",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1011111001 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[761, 1371, 2f9]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "211",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -39 in 13-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[0000000100110]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "212",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 4.73, Theta: 1.9, Phi: 1.13) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[1.91, 4.05, -1.53]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "213",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 4.46, Y: 1.94, Z: -5.51) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[7.35, 2.42, 0.41]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "214",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 6.85 and phase 5.51 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[4.9, -4.78]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "215",
    "question": "Rotate the point (6.05, 8.03) by an angle 6.0 radians.",
    "answer": "[[8.05, 6.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "216",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 53.35 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 24.52 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 93.44 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.05, 5335.0, 0.0, 93440.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "217",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-2.64, -4.0, -4.38) around the axis (-0.7, -0.25, -0.67) by an angle 4.38 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-3.01, 0.61, -5.73]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "218",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-8.34, 1.24, 7.49), (9.62, -6.68, -7.03) and (8.56, 8.23, 4.92), (-1.85, -9.32, 7.33).",
    "answer": "[[-1.35, -1.84, 1.84]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "219",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-1.77, 2.74, 8.5):\n[[-0.04 -0.99 -0.28  6.84]\n [ 0.63  0.27 -0.88  9.94]\n [ 0.89  0.94 -0.75  1.11]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[1.82, 2.08, -4.26]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "220",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (4.06, 8.63, 8.87) to the plane with the equation 4.04x + -8.08y + -9.39z + 4.21 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[10.16]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "221",
    "question": "Project the point (0.97, -2.39, -9.34) onto the line passing through points (3.73, -1.43, 3.77) and (7.23, -9.37, 6.45).",
    "answer": "[[2.15, 2.15, 2.56]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "222",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-8.62, 9.91) around the center point (8.18, -4.03) by an angle 4.84 radians.",
    "answer": "[[19.87, 14.41]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "223",
    "question": "Project the point (-0.86, 7.48, -1.05) onto the plane with the equation -8.24x + -5.07y + -8.24z + 4.11 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-1.78, 6.91, -1.97]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "224",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-2.15, 2.77, 7.59) around the axis (-0.5, 0.58, -0.64) by an angle 2.94 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[5.5, -4.18, -4.71]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "225",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-7.41+1.82j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[7.63, 2.9]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "226",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 6.06, Angle: 0.19) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[5.95, 1.14]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "227",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 496 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[111110000, 760, 1f0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "228",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 100000000 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[256, 400, 100]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "229",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 96 in 14-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[11111110011111]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "230",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 6.95, Theta: 2.48, Phi: 4.84) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[0.54, -4.24, -5.48]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "231",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 2.11, Y: 4.08, Z: -1.79) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[4.93, 1.94, 1.09]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "232",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 1.9 and phase 3.77 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-1.54, -1.12]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "233",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-2.25, -2.93) by an angle 6.06 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-2.84, -2.36]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "234",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 40.55 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 96.89 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 64.74 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.04, 4055.0, 0.0, 64740.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "235",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-8.19, 7.21, -5.06) around the axis (-0.06, 0.28, 0.96) by an angle 4.67 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[8.82, 7.17, -3.99]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "236",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (0.91, 7.47, 7.42), (3.87, 2.98, -7.69) and (6.04, -8.65, -5.31), (3.79, 9.62, 9.95).",
    "answer": "[[0.93, 7.44, 7.32]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "237",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-2.45, 2.2, -7.52):\n[[-0.57 -0.26  0.77 -7.19]\n [ 0.37 -0.12 -0.82  2.53]\n [ 0.13  0.86 -0.92 -3.46]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-12.16, 7.53, 5.03]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "238",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-9.79, 1.16, -3.08) to the plane with the equation 6.69x + -5.93y + 5.78z + 3.68 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[8.13]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "239",
    "question": "Project the point (1.44, 4.17, 6.4) onto the line passing through points (-4.25, 7.04, -3.17) and (-5.39, 2.76, 7.12).",
    "answer": "[[-5.2, 3.48, 5.38]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "240",
    "question": "Rotate the point (0.26, -3.34) around the center point (-3.27, -2.83) by an angle 1.04 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-1.04, -0.04]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "241",
    "question": "Project the point (7.33, 0.89, 2.04) onto the plane with the equation 3.91x + -0.44y + 8.96z + -8.48 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[5.78, 1.06, -1.52]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "242",
    "question": "Rotate the point (2.24, -4.16, 3.07) around the axis (0.77, 0.29, 0.57) by an angle 1.31 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[5.03, -1.63, -1.97]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "243",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-3.44+9.72j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[10.31, 1.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "244",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 6.58, Angle: 3.31) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-6.49, -1.1]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "245",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 489 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[111101001, 751, 1e9]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "246",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 11010010 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[210, 322, d2]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "247",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -15 in 12-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[000000001110]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "248",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 8.1, Theta: 1.39, Phi: 3.32) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-7.84, -1.41, 1.46]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "249",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 2.76, Y: 7.97, Z: 4.13) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[9.39, 1.12, 1.24]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "250",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 4.4 and phase 1.12 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.92, 3.96]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "251",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-8.05, -2.43) by an angle 1.17 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-0.9, -8.36]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "252",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 35.98 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 3.31 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 51.85 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.04, 3598.0, 0.0, 51850.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "253",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.3, -6.13, 9.57) around the axis (0.56, -0.75, 0.35) by an angle 1.32 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[2.49, -11.0, 8.39]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "254",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (-4.21, 8.12, 2.83), (3.93, 2.09, -9.32) and (1.16, 0.96, -4.79), (4.53, -7.53, -2.26).",
    "answer": "[[1.14, 4.16, -5.16]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "255",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-5.55, 4.88, -4.66):\n[[ 0.48  0.63  0.9  -9.96]\n [ 0.93  0.69 -0.69 -1.52]\n [ 0.01 -0.73 -0.4  -2.82]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-13.74, -0.1, -4.57]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "256",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-0.78, -9.3, 5.02) to the plane with the equation -2.11x + 2.96y + -5.17z + -3.25 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[8.72]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "257",
    "question": "Project the point (2.87, 7.3, 4.14) onto the line passing through points (0.28, -4.5, 5.53) and (-5.06, -7.17, -5.85).",
    "answer": "[[1.23, -4.02, 7.56]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "258",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-7.0, 5.94) around the center point (0.59, 4.41) by an angle 1.99 radians.",
    "answer": "[[2.28, -3.15]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "259",
    "question": "Project the point (0.51, 7.13, -7.26) onto the plane with the equation -5.31x + 4.61y + 8.47z + -3.57 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-1.02, 8.46, -4.82]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "260",
    "question": "Rotate the point (1.65, 9.19, -9.88) around the axis (-0.2, 0.75, 0.64) by an angle 2.85 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-5.5, -8.72, 8.88]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "261",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-5.36+1.02j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[5.46, 2.95]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "262",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 5.97, Angle: 3.08) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-5.96, 0.37]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "263",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 226 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[11100010, 342, e2]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "264",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1011110000 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[752, 1360, 2f0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "265",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -68 in 11-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[00001000011]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "266",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 7.82, Theta: 0.63, Phi: 5.96) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[4.37, -1.46, 6.32]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "267",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -8.4, Y: -6.45, Z: 3.75) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[11.23, 1.23, -2.49]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "268",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 3.81 and phase 3.42 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-3.66, -1.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "269",
    "question": "Rotate the point (2.06, 8.52) by an angle 2.1 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-8.39, -2.52]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "270",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 58.15 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 20.88 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 45.68 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.06, 5815.0, 0.0, 45680.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "271",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-7.07, 8.08, 4.28) around the axis (0.48, -0.87, 0.07) by an angle 3.81 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-0.47, 10.96, -3.22]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "272",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (9.76, -1.55, -6.61), (-5.31, 4.9, -8.67) and (2.55, -8.61, -5.39), (-8.45, -9.25, -0.91).",
    "answer": "[[14.69, -3.66, -5.94]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "273",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-9.82, -5.09, -2.45):\n[[ 0.87 -0.13 -0.71  2.7 ]\n [-0.54  0.57 -0.74  8.93]\n [-0.38 -0.36  0.58  9.57]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-3.44, 13.14, 13.71]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "274",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-3.7, -6.06, -2.5) to the plane with the equation -6.95x + -1.11y + 1.42z + 6.15 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[4.88]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "275",
    "question": "Project the point (9.37, -0.96, -7.97) onto the line passing through points (1.64, -0.48, 9.89) and (-3.77, -0.86, 8.33).",
    "answer": "[[3.98, -0.32, 10.56]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "276",
    "question": "Rotate the point (6.4, 3.08) around the center point (4.79, 4.79) by an angle 6.24 radians.",
    "answer": "[[6.32, 3.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "277",
    "question": "Project the point (-0.62, 3.05, -8.83) onto the plane with the equation 3.15x + 3.2y + -7.52z + 7.45 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-3.97, -0.36, -0.83]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "278",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-4.97, -7.53, 4.51) around the axis (-0.5, 0.56, 0.66) by an angle 5.99 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-6.95, -6.88, 2.46]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "279",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-2+2.52j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[3.22, 2.24]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "280",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 5.77, Angle: 6.25) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[5.77, -0.19]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "281",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 690 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1010110010, 1262, 2b2]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "282",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1110000011 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[899, 1603, 383]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "283",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 83 in 16-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[1111111110101100]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "284",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 9.46, Theta: 1.07, Phi: 1.47) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[0.84, 8.26, 4.54]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "285",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -5.02, Y: 9.69, Z: -5.51) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[12.23, 2.04, 2.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "286",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 8.05 and phase 1.6 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-0.24, 8.05]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "287",
    "question": "Rotate the point (5.31, -9.76) by an angle 5.9 radians.",
    "answer": "[[1.28, -11.04]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "288",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 24.89 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 8.43 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 78.94 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.02, 2489.0, 0.0, 78940.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "289",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-4.11, -2.52, 3.53) around the axis (0.55, 0.66, -0.51) by an angle 3.94 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-3.23, -4.77, 1.54]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "290",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (8.94, -4.61, -6.51), (8.15, -1.33, 3.56) and (7.08, -6.06, 4.38), (-2.76, 5.75, -4.6).",
    "answer": "[[8.25, -1.75, 2.27]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "291",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-9.7, 7.79, -7.38):\n[[ 0.72  0.78  0.72  1.67]\n [ 0.32 -0.72  0.32 -1.96]\n [-0.79  0.74 -0.76 -4.55]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-4.55, -13.03, 14.49]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "292",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (-4.59, -1.08, -1.04) to the plane with the equation 8.22x + -1.81y + -2.67z + 7.83 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[2.85]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "293",
    "question": "Project the point (4.24, -4.96, 1.75) onto the line passing through points (4.96, 6.89, -1.18) and (6.89, 6.68, 1.55).",
    "answer": "[[6.52, 6.72, 1.03]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "294",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-8.85, -5.9) around the center point (-2.49, 9.91) by an angle 2.46 radians.",
    "answer": "[[12.41, 18.18]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "295",
    "question": "Project the point (5.17, 0.12, 7.36) onto the plane with the equation -6.83x + -4.61y + -5.25z + 4.13 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[0.14, -3.28, 3.49]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "296",
    "question": "Rotate the point (1.64, 9.66, 8.84) around the axis (-0.51, 0.43, 0.75) by an angle 1.69 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-9.29, 9.33, 1.7]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "297",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-0.4-9.82j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[9.83, -1.61]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "298",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 4.53, Angle: 1.38) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[0.86, 4.45]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "299",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 408 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[110011000, 630, 198]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "300",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1101110011 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[883, 1563, 373]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "301",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 88 in 15-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[111111110100111]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "302",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 2.34, Theta: 1.09, Phi: 1.02) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[1.09, 1.77, 1.08]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "303",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: 2.19, Y: -8.89, Z: -4.07) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[10.02, 1.99, -1.33]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "304",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 1.71 and phase 2.16 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-0.95, 1.42]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "305",
    "question": "Rotate the point (3.18, 7.52) by an angle 4.78 radians.",
    "answer": "[[7.72, -2.66]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "306",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 94.41 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 60.41 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 43.79 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.09, 9441.0, 0.0, 43790.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "307",
    "question": "Rotate the point (3.58, -8.82, -8.57) around the axis (-0.33, -0.9, 0.3) by an angle 4.94 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-10.35, -3.2, -6.94]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "308",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (3.62, 7.91, -8.56), (-5.21, -4.71, -4.04) and (5.21, -6.28, 0.73), (5.86, 3.34, -6.18).",
    "answer": "[[5.59, 10.72, -9.57]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "309",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (0.45, -9.06, -5.57):\n[[ 0.36  0.01 -0.22 -6.23]\n [ 0.23 -0.29 -0.96  3.02]\n [-0.99  0.39  0.16 -2.03]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-4.93, 11.1, -6.9]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "310",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (9.71, -0.18, 7.67) to the plane with the equation -0.29x + 8.17y + -7.84z + 5.35 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[5.21]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "311",
    "question": "Project the point (7.92, -4.4, 0.6) onto the line passing through points (1.25, 3.53, -5.08) and (3.41, 2.56, -4.98).",
    "answer": "[[9.97, -0.38, -4.68]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "312",
    "question": "Rotate the point (6.16, -2.64) around the center point (7.85, -8.71) by an angle 5.49 radians.",
    "answer": "[[10.99, -3.25]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "313",
    "question": "Project the point (-1.78, 0.48, -8.6) onto the plane with the equation -4.78x + 1.75y + 8.57z + 5.6 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-4.61, 1.51, -3.53]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "314",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.55, 5.87, 9.78) around the axis (0.58, 0.77, 0.27) by an angle 2.14 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[11.22, 8.36, -2.91]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "315",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-7.57+0.76j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[7.61, 3.04]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "316",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 8.7, Angle: 1.26) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[2.66, 8.28]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "317",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 627 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1001110011, 1163, 273]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "318",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1111000010 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[962, 1702, 3c2]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "319",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 60 in 8-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[11000011]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "320",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 1.12, Theta: 1.41, Phi: 1.42) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[0.17, 1.09, 0.18]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "321",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -0.95, Y: -3.22, Z: -4.44) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[5.57, 2.49, -1.86]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "322",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 6.32 and phase 4.26 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-2.76, -5.68]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "323",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-8.87, -6.53) by an angle 0.49 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-4.75, -9.94]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "324",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 31.31 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 95.89 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 25.0 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.03, 3131.0, 0.0, 25000.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "325",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-9.34, 9.07, -2.6) around the axis (0.28, 0.34, -0.9) by an angle 0.47 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-4.95, 12.33, -0.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "326",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (9.43, -6.37, -2.05), (3.45, -2.31, 7.37) and (-3.63, -4.17, -3.61), (-2.17, 2.36, -3.96).",
    "answer": "[[6.2, -4.18, 3.04]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "327",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (7.11, 4.57, 8.07):\n[[-0.12  0.48 -0.66 -5.76]\n [ 0.91 -0.66 -0.54 -1.71]\n [-0.18 -0.88 -0.52  1.48]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[-9.75, -2.61, -8.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "328",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (3.24, -2.36, 7.75) to the plane with the equation -2.71x + -5.57y + 1.51z + 9.37 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[3.99]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "329",
    "question": "Project the point (1.42, 9.69, -8.08) onto the line passing through points (-1.06, -4.26, 1.06) and (6.73, -6.61, 6.52).",
    "answer": "[[-6.2, -2.71, -2.54]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "330",
    "question": "Rotate the point (7.77, -9.79) around the center point (-1.77, 2.4) by an angle 3.41 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-14.2, 11.62]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "331",
    "question": "Project the point (2.39, -7.56, 9.61) onto the plane with the equation -2.64x + 0.41y + 9.3z + -1.27 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[4.61, -7.9, 1.79]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "332",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-6.95, -5.79, -8.11) around the axis (-0.42, 0.09, 0.9) by an angle 4.08 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[3.77, 10.51, -4.69]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "333",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (3.98+1.98j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[4.45, 0.46]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "334",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 1.45, Angle: 3.01) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-1.44, 0.19]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "335",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 991 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1111011111, 1737, 3df]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "336",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 110000001 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[385, 601, 181]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "337",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number 86 in 12-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[111110101001]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "338",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 2.5, Theta: 0.77, Phi: 2.2) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[-1.02, 1.41, 1.79]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "339",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -6.11, Y: -3.09, Z: 1.05) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[6.93, 1.42, -2.67]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "340",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 9.8 and phase 2.94 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[-9.6, 1.96]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "341",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-3.15, 5.52) by an angle 0.74 radians.",
    "answer": "[[-6.05, 1.95]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "342",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 76.33 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 42.78 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 87.56 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.08, 7633.0, 0.0, 87560.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "343",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-8.96, -6.85, 8.42) around the axis (0.68, 0.28, -0.68) by an angle 4.1 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[-7.68, -2.42, 11.63]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "344",
    "question": "Determine the intersection point of the lines passing through points (6.56, 1.27, -5.73), (5.9, -4.62, 2.8) and (2.76, 0.23, 3.67), (-8.93, -3.73, -5.05).",
    "answer": "[[6.01, -3.6, 1.33]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "345",
    "question": "Apply the following 4x4 transformation matrix to the point (-0.93, -7.11, 5.46):\n[[ 0.63  0.27  0.62  4.76]\n [ 0.39 -0.66 -0.22  0.66]\n [-0.85  0.93 -0.03  0.06]\n [ 0.    0.    0.    1.  ]]",
    "answer": "[[5.64, 3.79, -5.93]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "346",
    "question": "Compute the perpendicular distance from the point (7.5, 3.0, 7.67) to the plane with the equation -9.44x + 4.31y + -4.81z + 0.42 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[8.25]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "347",
    "question": "Project the point (1.1, -3.26, -5.79) onto the line passing through points (-5.43, -4.23, 4.28) and (-9.83, 5.83, 8.94).",
    "answer": "[[-3.39, -8.89, 2.12]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "348",
    "question": "Rotate the point (-0.46, -1.11) around the center point (-3.78, -3.86) by an angle 5.94 radians.",
    "answer": "[[0.27, -2.39]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "349",
    "question": "Project the point (-8.67, 8.42, 9.38) onto the plane with the equation -4.04x + -5.67y + 1.86z + 2.75 = 0.",
    "answer": "[[-8.09, 9.24, 9.11]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "350",
    "question": "Rotate the point (7.31, -9.48, -2.24) around the axis (-0.89, -0.44, 0.15) by an angle 5.14 radians. Answer in the format [[x_rot, y_rot, z_rot]]",
    "answer": "[[2.23, -2.43, -11.77]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "351",
    "question": "Convert the complex number (-3.03+2.24j) to polar form (Amplitude, Angle in radians).",
    "answer": "[[3.77, 2.5]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "352",
    "question": "Convert the polar coordinates (Amplitude: 1.32, Angle: 5.38) to rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[0.82, -1.04]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "353",
    "question": "Convert the decimal number 877 to binary, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[binary, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[1101101101, 1555, 36d]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "354",
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1100100110 to decimal, octal, and hexadecimal. Answer in the format [[decimal, octal, hexadecimal]]",
    "answer": "[[806, 1446, 326]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "355",
    "question": "Find the one's complement of the number -82 in 12-bit representation.",
    "answer": "[[000001010001]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "356",
    "question": "Convert the spherical coordinates (Radius: 4.01, Theta: 0.4, Phi: 0.98) to Cartesian coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[0.87, 1.3, 3.69]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "357",
    "question": "Convert the Cartesian coordinates (X: -5.06, Y: 2.71, Z: -8.01) to spherical coordinates.",
    "answer": "[[9.85, 2.52, 2.65]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "358",
    "question": "Convert the amplitude 1.92 and phase 0.62 to the complex number in rectangular form.",
    "answer": "[[1.56, 1.12]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "359",
    "question": "Rotate the point (8.23, -2.4) by an angle 1.74 radians.",
    "answer": "[[0.98, 8.52]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "360",
    "question": "Convert the following units:\n- Length: 81.77 meters to kilometers and centimeters\n- Area: 26.55 square meters to square kilometers\n- Volume: 90.65 cubic meters to liters",
    "answer": "[[0.08, 8177.0, 0.0, 90650.0]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "361",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [-5.94, 9.3, 1.49]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [0.15, -1.64, -2.92]\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-5.79, -7.66, 1.43]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "362",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [-5.68, -8.41, 1.02]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.13, 1.22, 1.8]\nStep 3: Rotate by 2.78 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 2\nStep 4: Rotate by 5.79 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 2\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-6.53, 10.29, 1.37]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "363",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [2.18, -2.54, 1.19]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [-0.13, 0.61, 3.32]\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.96, 1.53, 1.06]\nStep 3: Rotate by 1.59 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 1\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 5: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.88, 1.39, 1.78]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-2.53, 5.67, 8.51]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "364",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [-7.4, -1.68, 5.14]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 2: Translate by [2.58, -2.58, 2.6]\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 4: Translate by [-1.88, 0.53, 2.28]\nStep 5: Translate by [4.39, -0.46, -0.96]\nStep 6: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.81, 1.48, 1.34]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[13.27, -6.20, -1.63]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "365",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [0.21, 9.55, -7.62]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [3.79, -5.0, 2.03]\nStep 2: Rotate by 4.60 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 2\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.63, 1.31, 0.91]\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 1\nStep 6: Rotate by 2.60 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 2\nStep 7: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 7.90, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "366",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [0.28, 5.76, 4.26]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [0.17, 2.21, 1.07]\nStep 2: Rotate by 4.70 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 2\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.07, 1.32, 1.61]\nStep 5: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.78, 0.69, 1.35]\nStep 6: Rotate by 1.89 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 0\nStep 7: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 8: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.92, 0.68, 0.52]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[2.22, -4.94, -2.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "367",
    "question": "Start with a point in 3-dimensional space: [-2.09, -2.9, 4.38]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [-3.51, 4.12, 1.77]\nStep 2: Rotate by 4.99 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 0\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.92, 0.78, 1.38]\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.62, 1.32, 1.11]\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 6: Translate by [3.63, -1.69, -2.91]\nStep 7: Translate by [-3.17, 2.66, -4.49]\nStep 8: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.69, 1.46, 1.69]\nStep 9: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-7.93, 3.25, -22.14]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "368",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [6.58, -5.14, -2.14, 1.97]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [1.95, -3.35, -1.8, 4.16]\nStep 2: Translate by [-4.31, -3.94, 4.92, -0.52]\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 0\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[4.22, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "369",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [-4.91, 9.77, 1.95, -8.15]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 4.79 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 1\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 0\nStep 3: Rotate by 3.51 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 2\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.87, 1.29, 0.85, 0.91]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-9.18, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "370",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [4.86, 4.65, -3.14, 5.78]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [-0.09, 1.15, 0.3, 3.41]\nStep 2: Translate by [-0.91, -1.35, 0.78, -3.97]\nStep 3: Rotate by 2.90 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 0\nStep 4: Rotate by 3.06 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 0\nStep 5: Rotate by 0.42 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[3.10, -5.61, 0.27, -5.01]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "371",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [-2.66, -9.88, 4.33, -2.18]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 2: Rotate by 0.20 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 1\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nStep 4: Translate by [-2.33, 1.43, 1.43, 2.2]\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 3\nStep 6: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.33, -10.25, 7.65, -0.02]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "372",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [-2.73, -3.62, 8.72, -7.77]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 3\nStep 4: Project onto the axis 0\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 1\nStep 6: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 7: Rotate by 1.68 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 3\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "373",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [8.1, -8.81, 7.03, 4.45]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.73, 1.69, 1.23, 1.62]\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 3: Rotate by 0.23 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 2\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 5: Translate by [-0.84, 4.27, 2.69, -1.02]\nStep 6: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.96, 1.8, 1.23, 1.45]\nStep 7: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.32, 1.5, 1.05, 1.58]\nStep 8: Rotate by 0.24 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 0\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-15.18, -25.76, -9.51, 9.12]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "374",
    "question": "Start with a point in 4-dimensional space: [2.33, -1.36, 6.34, 6.81]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 5.66 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 2\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.02, 0.73, 0.81, 0.82]\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.52, 1.09, 1.0, 1.64]\nStep 4: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 3\nStep 6: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.83, 0.86, 1.89, 0.95]\nStep 7: Rotate by 3.69 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 1\nStep 8: Rotate by 2.55 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 3\nStep 9: Translate by [-0.01, 2.12, 1.27, 3.57]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-0.01, 2.12, 1.27, 3.57]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "375",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [1.36, -2.99, 6.21, -8.98, 4.02]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [-1.1, 0.08, 4.73, -4.69, 3.07]\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 1\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 2\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "376",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [-7.55, -0.84, 1.91, 9.0, 4.01]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.64, 0.75, 1.51, 0.63, 1.47]\nStep 2: Translate by [-2.97, -4.35, 3.43, -1.79, 2.28]\nStep 3: Translate by [-3.25, -0.44, -0.26, -3.07, -4.92]\nStep 4: Translate by [-3.36, 2.28, -0.65, -0.98, -3.49]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-21.96, -3.14, 5.40, -0.17, -0.24]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "377",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [1.97, -6.38, -3.96, -1.57, 8.7]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.37, 1.43, 1.45, 1.3, 1.07]\nStep 2: Rotate by 3.46 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 4\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.96, 0.52, 1.09, 0.82, 1.09]\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.11, 1.58, 1.74, 0.85, 1.59]\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.70, 7.49, -10.89, -1.42, -16.78]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "378",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [-9.23, -7.16, 3.27, -8.19, -9.09]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [2.34, -0.31, -2.59, -1.58, -2.97]\nStep 2: Rotate by 6.01 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 2\nStep 3: Rotate by 2.68 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 2\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.53, 1.87, 1.72, 1.8, 1.75]\nStep 5: Translate by [-2.15, -2.4, -4.09, 1.67, -0.96]\nStep 6: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-5.80, -7.12, -13.64, -15.92, -22.06]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "379",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [-2.12, 7.06, 1.75, -7.23, -7.77]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 4\nStep 2: Rotate by 4.71 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 3\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 4: Rotate by 4.67 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 3\nStep 5: Translate by [3.06, -1.08, 0.54, -4.47, 2.55]\nStep 6: Rotate by 2.98 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 1\nStep 7: Project onto the axis 3\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 4.60, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "380",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [-1.37, 6.29, 2.98, 8.64, -2.15]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.87, 0.76, 1.02, 0.89, 1.17]\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 3\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 5: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.82, 0.86, 1.42, 1.22, 0.55]\nStep 6: Translate by [1.13, -1.95, -4.92, -4.42, -3.64]\nStep 7: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 8: Project onto the axis 2\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 4.92, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "381",
    "question": "Start with a point in 5-dimensional space: [-9.3, -7.98, 7.82, -4.53, 8.16]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 2: Rotate by 6.03 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 2\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.64, 1.76, 1.33, 0.81, 1.12]\nStep 4: Rotate by 2.24 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 4\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 4\nStep 6: Rotate by 3.31 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 4\nStep 7: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.51, 0.51, 1.57, 0.83, 1.51]\nStep 8: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 9: Project onto the axis 2\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "382",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [-7.35, 2.44, 1.1, -8.19, -2.14, -8.98]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 0.00 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 5 and 0\nStep 2: Rotate by 3.19 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 0\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.74, 1.46, 1.82, 0.58, 1.15, 1.05]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[5.74, 3.56, 2.00, 4.54, -2.46, -9.43]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "383",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [6.42, 2.06, -3.62, -9.03, -8.16, 7.16]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [4.42, 3.64, -3.94, 1.06, -3.39, 3.39]\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.48, 0.53, 1.21, 1.9, 0.8, 1.16]\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.52, 1.01, 1.72, 0.73, 0.62, 1.41]\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.4, 1.85, 0.53, 1.82, 1.95, 1.33]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[11.68, 5.64, -8.34, -20.12, -11.17, 22.95]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "384",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [3.54, 3.13, -7.54, -0.69, -2.96, 1.96]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 0\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.36, 0.54, 0.83, 1.57, 1.52, 1.97]\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 4: Rotate by 3.80 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 0\nStep 5: Rotate by 0.29 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 0\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-3.65, 2.94, 1.10, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "385",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [4.1, -4.28, 2.39, -1.8, 6.04, 3.58]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 3\nStep 3: Rotate by 6.12 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 3\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.49, 1.06, 0.78, 0.65, 1.37, 0.55]\nStep 5: Rotate by 2.81 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 4\nStep 6: Rotate by 1.08 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 4\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-0.43, 0.00, 0.00, -1.16, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "386",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [5.12, 9.52, 2.04, -9.39, -2.22, -7.2]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 1.54 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 5\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.99, 1.04, 1.9, 1.4, 0.62, 1.18]\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 5\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.93, 1.34, 1.26, 1.43, 1.64, 0.78]\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 5\nStep 6: Perform axial symmetry along axis 3\nStep 7: Translate by [-0.04, -4.4, -3.17, 0.23, -0.71, -4.89]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-0.04, -4.40, -3.17, 0.23, -0.71, 3.96]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "387",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [-1.79, -7.72, -9.78, 6.79, -5.38, 9.04]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.23, 1.52, 0.86, 1.53, 0.58, 1.9]\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 4: Translate by [3.64, 2.18, 2.37, 1.91, 2.81, -1.74]\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 3\nStep 6: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 7: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.78, 1.83, 1.28, 1.61, 0.94, 1.85]\nStep 8: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.31, 0.55, 1.13, 1.59, 0.58, 1.29]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[1.47, -9.62, 8.74, -31.48, -0.17, 36.84]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "388",
    "question": "Start with a point in 6-dimensional space: [-2.18, 5.9, 8.08, 7.6, 4.94, 8.61]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.86, 1.72, 1.29, 0.66, 1.32, 1.83]\nStep 2: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.54, 1.17, 1.5, 1.96, 0.87, 1.15]\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 5: Translate by [-3.18, -4.01, 4.05, 0.31, -0.73, -4.13]\nStep 6: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 7: Rotate by 4.71 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 5\nStep 8: Rotate by 0.79 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 4 and 5\nStep 9: Translate by [-4.84, 4.66, -2.75, -1.87, 4.9, -0.8]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-4.84, 4.66, 16.93, -1.87, 4.90, -0.80]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "389",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [9.41, 2.7, 7.18, 5.62, -8.81, 1.37, -2.68]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.66, 0.69, 0.87, 1.33, 1.09, 1.65, 1.37]\nStep 2: Translate by [0.76, -1.58, 0.58, -3.65, -4.26, -4.76, -4.74]\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 2\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 6.83, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "390",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [-3.69, -8.12, -1.6, 7.98, -0.06, -4.66, 8.25]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 0\nStep 2: Translate by [0.45, -4.09, -0.8, 2.96, -1.4, -0.46, -4.88]\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 4: Translate by [4.6, 4.77, -2.15, 3.12, 2.35, 2.67, 2.0]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[4.60, 4.77, -2.95, 3.12, 2.35, 2.67, 2.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "391",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [4.33, -1.97, 6.11, 0.66, -9.56, -8.66, -5.87]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 4.95 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 5\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 5\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 6.11, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "392",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [4.96, 3.36, -0.57, -0.66, -0.46, -3.26, 8.05]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 4\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 3: Translate by [2.19, 1.8, 2.99, -2.2, -1.03, 1.39, 0.94]\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.02, 1.55, 1.58, 0.98, 1.12, 1.65, 1.84]\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 4\nStep 6: Project onto the axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "393",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [-7.17, -3.87, -5.9, 0.29, -0.14, -3.29, 5.3]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.86, 0.96, 1.98, 0.75, 1.21, 1.86, 0.66]\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 3: Rotate by 4.59 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 5 and 4\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.37, 1.97, 0.6, 1.34, 1.59, 0.52, 1.89]\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 6: Translate by [-2.32, -2.88, -4.47, -4.58, -2.87, 1.7, 4.59]\nStep 7: Rotate by 2.47 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 4 and 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-2.32, 0.47, -11.48, -4.58, 4.02, 1.70, 4.59]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "394",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [7.61, -4.1, -9.96, 8.42, 0.31, -5.64, -5.23]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 5\nStep 2: Translate by [0.92, 2.58, 3.72, 3.41, -3.32, -3.58, 1.76]\nStep 3: Translate by [-0.8, -3.0, 2.07, -1.37, -0.56, 3.63, -2.27]\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.95, 0.53, 0.77, 1.93, 1.89, 1.51, 1.34]\nStep 5: Rotate by 2.98 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 6 and 0\nStep 6: Translate by [-1.5, -1.47, -0.54, 3.12, 0.08, 3.21, 4.24]\nStep 7: Translate by [0.95, 2.71, -2.84, -0.28, -4.57, -3.72, 0.2]\nStep 8: Rotate by 5.81 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 4 and 3\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-0.77, 1.02, 1.08, 11.47, -7.40, -8.95, 5.10]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "395",
    "question": "Start with a point in 7-dimensional space: [-3.31, 1.41, -0.61, 2.38, -9.86, -4.65, 2.46]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [-4.78, -3.06, -3.26, 1.97, -1.72, -2.39, 3.62]\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 6\nStep 3: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nStep 4: Translate by [-0.44, 1.26, 1.74, -3.43, 4.14, -3.44, 0.69]\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 1\nStep 6: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.92, 1.45, 1.18, 0.59, 0.85, 0.57, 1.52]\nStep 7: Translate by [-3.22, 0.68, 4.98, 1.56, -1.95, -2.56, 4.92]\nStep 8: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.09, 1.73, 1.32, 1.9, 1.25, 0.72, 0.74]\nStep 9: Rotate by 5.83 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 6 and 5\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-3.51, 0.20, 6.57, 2.96, -2.44, -3.26, 2.47]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "396",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [4.56, 2.5, 4.09, -1.23, -2.25, 5.18, 5.52, -5.37]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.65, 1.0, 0.59, 1.16, 1.32, 1.57, 1.35, 0.62]\nStep 2: Rotate by 0.58 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 1\nStep 3: Rotate by 2.51 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 7\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[2.96, -0.81, 0.65, -1.43, -2.97, 8.13, 7.45, 4.72]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "397",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [8.94, 6.92, 3.17, 4.38, 1.38, 2.44, -5.53, 4.18]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [1.54, -2.55, 1.09, -1.7, -3.55, -0.06, -0.55, 0.24]\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.85, 0.52, 0.55, 0.96, 0.85, 0.79, 1.96, 0.66]\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.41, 0.92, 0.73, 0.64, 0.98, 0.6, 1.34, 1.25]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 1.71, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "398",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [-3.03, -6.94, -5.89, 2.23, -2.94, -2.04, -6.71, 2.52]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 3.93 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 2\nStep 2: Translate by [0.89, -4.91, -4.35, -3.36, 2.3, 2.7, -1.79, 2.56]\nStep 3: Rotate by 0.19 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 0\nStep 4: Project onto the axis 7\nStep 5: Rotate by 0.03 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 6\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 5.08]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "399",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [-9.5, 7.05, -9.69, -9.54, -2.23, 1.87, -9.56, -8.23]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.81, 1.58, 1.29, 1.6, 1.29, 1.47, 1.15, 0.95]\nStep 2: Rotate by 4.05 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 4 and 2\nStep 3: Translate by [-2.26, 3.68, -0.18, -1.1, -4.4, -2.34, 2.87, 2.62]\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 7\nStep 5: Translate by [-4.59, -0.53, 1.6, 4.52, -2.37, 2.95, 2.47, -4.87]\nStep 6: Project onto the axis 3\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, -11.84, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "400",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [9.96, -8.38, -9.19, -1.22, -0.63, 7.93, -7.08, 6.88]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 4\nStep 2: Rotate by 1.71 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 3\nStep 3: Rotate by 0.97 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 5 and 4\nStep 4: Rotate by 4.52 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 5\nStep 5: Translate by [-0.13, 1.92, 2.78, 3.6, -3.52, -3.78, 2.27, -1.61]\nStep 6: Perform axial symmetry along axis 5\nStep 7: Project onto the axis 0\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-0.13, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "401",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [-9.76, 9.22, -0.97, 6.71, -8.92, -4.21, -0.73, 8.59]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 0\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 3\nStep 3: Rotate by 4.11 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 1\nStep 4: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 5: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 6: Rotate by 3.73 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 5 and 6\nStep 7: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.01, 1.69, 1.4, 1.5, 0.83, 0.72, 1.94, 1.89]\nStep 8: Perform axial symmetry along axis 4\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "402",
    "question": "Start with a point in 8-dimensional space: [-5.05, -2.45, -3.25, 9.03, -6.82, -5.68, -0.7, 1.11]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 4\nStep 3: Translate by [-4.68, 0.47, 1.59, 0.09, -3.89, -1.84, 4.14, -1.4]\nStep 4: Project onto the axis 7\nStep 5: Translate by [0.17, 2.56, 3.58, -1.66, 1.91, -3.45, 4.2, -3.3]\nStep 6: Project onto the axis 0\nStep 7: Rotate by 1.40 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 7\nStep 8: Translate by [2.74, -3.38, 1.81, 2.87, 1.31, 4.64, -0.43, 2.25]\nStep 9: Rotate by 4.64 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 4\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[2.91, -3.38, 1.81, 1.11, -2.96, 4.64, -0.43, 2.25]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "403",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [8.49, 1.73, -5.96, 8.75, -2.5, 0.67, 6.97, 4.2, -7.37]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Project onto the axis 0\nStep 2: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 3: Translate by [1.15, -0.74, 4.55, 3.53, 3.74, 3.27, 2.4, -3.01, -2.74]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[1.15, -0.74, 4.55, 3.53, 3.74, 3.27, 2.40, -3.01, -2.74]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "404",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [5.01, 0.31, -2.65, -2.21, -8.46, 2.61, -9.08, 6.47, -5.92]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [-1.27, 0.26, 1.49, -3.69, 3.56, 4.4, -3.02, -4.09, -0.82]\nStep 2: Rotate by 2.68 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 5\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.82, 1.18, 0.51, 0.86, 1.23, 0.92, 1.55, 0.93, 0.78]\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 1\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[-11.87, -0.67, -0.59, -5.07, -6.03, -4.26, -18.76, 2.21, -5.26]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "405",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [-4.18, -2.57, 5.56, -7.63, 7.85, -6.16, -0.45, 7.51, 7.0]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 4.03 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 2 and 4\nStep 2: Rotate by 5.39 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 8 and 0\nStep 3: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.87, 0.53, 1.14, 1.6, 0.61, 1.79, 1.85, 1.43, 1.04]\nStep 4: Translate by [1.38, 0.57, 1.67, 1.82, -4.35, -2.14, -3.0, 3.88, -2.51]\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 4\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, -10.01, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "406",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [1.37, -2.47, -2.42, -7.7, -1.28, -1.9, -5.01, -3.04, -7.63]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Translate by [4.4, -0.23, -3.7, 3.83, 1.36, 1.5, -3.71, -4.16, -1.27]\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 7\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 7\nStep 4: Perform axial symmetry along axis 3\nStep 5: Rotate by 1.97 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 3 and 7\nStep 6: Rotate by 5.06 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 6 and 4\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, -6.62, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, -2.81, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "407",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [2.28, 4.14, -4.51, 4.5, 8.85, 1.1, -0.61, 2.38, 8.84]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Rotate by 4.96 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 4 and 6\nStep 2: Translate by [-4.03, 0.31, -0.64, -3.48, -4.35, -0.97, 1.82, 2.14, -4.57]\nStep 3: Project onto the axis 6\nStep 4: Translate by [-2.05, -1.49, -2.42, 4.43, 1.39, -4.15, -2.35, -2.44, 3.18]\nStep 5: Project onto the axis 2\nStep 6: Rotate by 3.89 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 8 and 5\nStep 7: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.67, 1.37, 0.52, 0.68, 0.98, 0.74, 1.47, 1.95, 0.6]\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, -1.26, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "408",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [-5.72, -0.74, 6.29, -4.12, 8.21, -9.22, -1.12, -4.44, -1.79]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Squeeze by scaling factors [1.79, 1.97, 1.06, 1.34, 1.77, 1.36, 1.28, 1.43, 1.97]\nStep 2: Rotate by 4.19 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 8 and 3\nStep 3: Rotate by 2.01 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 8\nStep 4: Project onto the axis 8\nStep 5: Rotate by 4.16 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 5 and 8\nStep 6: Perform axial symmetry along axis 6\nStep 7: Translate by [-2.82, 3.93, -0.72, -0.36, -4.62, -4.18, -2.98, 3.34, 1.43]\nStep 8: Project onto the axis 8\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 5.60]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  },
  {
    "idx": "409",
    "question": "Start with a point in 9-dimensional space: [0.44, 5.06, 3.15, -5.88, -1.65, -2.48, 3.44, -0.99, 1.97]\nApply the following transformations in order:\nStep 1: Perform axial symmetry along axis 6\nStep 2: Perform axial symmetry along axis 2\nStep 3: Rotate by 6.16 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 5\nStep 4: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.81, 0.65, 1.24, 1.58, 1.08, 1.08, 1.98, 1.92, 1.26]\nStep 5: Squeeze by scaling factors [0.59, 1.51, 1.16, 0.9, 1.17, 0.74, 1.74, 1.26, 0.97]\nStep 6: Rotate by 2.79 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 1 and 7\nStep 7: Perform axial symmetry along axis 8\nStep 8: Project onto the axis 8\nStep 9: Rotate by 3.13 radians in the plane spanned by dimensions 0 and 7\nWhat are the final coordinates of the point after all the steps of transformations?",
    "answer": "[[0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, 0.00, -2.41]]",
    "rule_id": "1"
  }
]